

PROFILE

I am Enoch, a Full-Stack web developer and creative software engineer with 6+ years of experience in Web Development and professional software development. I deliver the solutions you want and need for your organization to reach your goals. I am a great team player and always ready to learn more as needed for the success of projects.

I don't just write and deliver codes; I develop solutions that scale. I have experience working with different brands and they have recorded massive success.

My Core Skills are HTML5, CSS, Figma, JavaScript, Bootstrap, Tailwind, jQuery, Vue JS, React JS, PHP, Laravel, Flutter, WordPress, MySQL, Python, SEO, APIs, Flutter, AWS, Azure, Docker, Git, and other programming languages.

CONTACT

PHONE:

+234 8074303908, +234 8151721148

WEBSITE:

bit.ly/enocholayode

EMAIL:

olayodeenoch@gmail.com

HOBBIES

Music Reading & Writing

OLAYODE ENOCH

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

EDUCATION

Adekunle Ajasin University, Akungba Akoko 2018 – 2023 – B.Sc. in Computer Science Awaiting Final Results

Barter by Flutterwave Student Ambassador (2020 – 2021) Google Developer Student Clubs Lead (2020 – 2021) Microsoft Learn Student Ambassador (2021 – 2023) Major League Hacking (MLH) Organizer (2020 – 2023)

The Ibarapa Polytechnic, Eruwa 2015 – 2017 – Diploma in Computer Science – 3.74 CGPA

WORK EXPERIENCE

Fiverr – Web Developer (Freelance)

2020 - Present

I have worked with divers international and national organizations to design, build, develop, debug, maintain, and deploy robust web and mobile applications.

ICTAC, Adekunle Ajasin University – Software Engineering Intern 2021 – I worked with a team of passionate students and to build technical solutions for the university including a campus map guide.

ICT, OYSCATECH – Software Engineering Intern 2016–2017

I worked with a team of professionals to manage and maintain the institution's software applications and servers.

SKILLS

